[{"answer": "Many times.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 5, "question": "Do you have had your heart broken?", "qSentId": 4}, {"answer": "If it's with you, I'm quite happy.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "How do you feel about being a prime time exclusive, Harry?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "That's a big -- that's a big compliment, because when you're chilling out by the pool and you want to put some music on, those are -- those are big decisions you -- you know, I feel very honored that you picked me.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "Do you like that?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "It's kind of -- I guess it's fast if I drive it fast.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "What's the matter with you?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "I've spoken to him a lot about it.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "But what could you say?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Yes, I have.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "But you've been through that terrible pain and grief when you were very young, haven't you?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "What feels amazing to me is how the city has not only rebuilt, but taken the devastation and found opportunity.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "It must feel strange to you, so long?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "ONNICK: And the America I know is the America that showed up and helped us build 80 houses for our musicians' village.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "When you see other weather-related disasters, most recently Oklahoma and going back to Joplin and the hurricanes, tornadoes, Hurricane Sandy here in -- on the East Coast, do you think that America, as a result of what happened in Katrina and all the controversy that came out, has America got better at dealing with the immediate aftermath of these things?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "I'd better look at my notes.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Is it too late?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Well, the song says --", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Now, come on, what should every man know?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "In many case, it -- I married my best friend.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "What do I need to do?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "My --", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "Do they even know what a CD is?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "I'm telling you, you know, thank God there are different ways to get music out there.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "They'd be like, dad, what -- what the hell is that piece of archaic old material?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "But is this a -- a generic song about love?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Is this you in an earlier incarnation?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Many times.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Did you have your heart broken?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "It's a horrible feeling.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "I try.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Do you sing to her in the bath?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "Wait, wait, who -- who's in the bath, me or her?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "ORGAN: (INAUDIBLE).", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "You know what happens?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know if you can decide to be a pop star, but if they said, dad, I'm going --", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "How do you feel if one of your girls said, dad, I've decided I'm going to be a pop star?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "No, no, no, I wouldn't mind at all.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "You wouldn't mind?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "Yes, I don't want them rootling around in my gear, mate.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "Do you care how much the government goes around your phone calls, emails?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "Today, I'm in a very good mood.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Russell, how are you?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Well, I like coming on the program --", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Why are you in a good mood?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "I love -- I enjoyed Friday and all of its sacred implications and I'm very happy to be with you, of course, across this prospect piece of wonderment, this geometrical division.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "The fact it's Friday?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "I think as an immigrant in this country, a good degree of caution is advised with these matters, as you yourself have experienced from your own outspoken views.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "But what -- what's your take on it?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "That's the definition of hero, is sacrificing yourself for others.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Are they heroes, though?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Because, you know, like I'm not a politician or anything.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "Is that heroic?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Yes, I don't want them rootling around in my gear, mate.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "ORGAN: Do you care how much a government rootles around your phone calls, e-mails?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Yes, I do, as a matter of fact.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "But do you care?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "I think that we have to test the veracity of their intention to protect before handing over such enormous power.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Because that's what it comes down to, how far are you prepared to let a government do that kind of thing in the name of protecting you and keeping your country safer from potential attacks?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "All right.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "I want to come back and ask the question that most of my viewers are asking every time you come on, where did you learn all these long words?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "It's all right (ph), because he's ever so -- he's got big strong, alpha tendencies and he was very wise.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "What was it like kissing Alec Baldwin?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Listen, in --", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Where did you learn to speak like this, seriously?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "RAND: Like, I like reading -- I like watching BBC comedies.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "Where did you learn to speak like this?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "No --", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "But when you were a young kid, you couldn't have been like seven or eight speaking like this, right?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "Yes, I went to a comprehensive school, that school at 15, didn't I?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "But did you study dictionaries?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "It's about all right, thank you very much.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "How is your love life?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Blooming.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Yes, blooming?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Why would she use that analogy, do you think?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "I'm going to show you a picture of your ex --", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "-- much are you going to go on about this (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "-- cavorting --", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Why would you do this?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "The Messiah Complex is a disorder where the sufferer believes himself to be God's anointed chosen one on Earth to bring about, you know, peace or whatever.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "What is The Messiah Complex?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Yes, it's true.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Yes, because I'm not accusing these people of having the messiah complex, I just like that pun.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "And who are the kind of people that you're going to be talking about in relation to the -- the kind of godlike figures?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "It's nice to do a movie if you're with Alec Baldwin or Helen Mirren or Jonah Hill or Jason Segel.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "What is the great love for Russell Brand, really?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "RAND: For me, I think it's about trying to overcome relentless egotism and selfishness.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "What is the -- what is the path to happiness for Russell Brand, do you think?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "There's really no secret.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "What's the secret?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "No, but I wish I did.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "Punishing, grueling gym sessions like I have to?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "Well, you know, especially as a kid growing up in Kentucky, there's a lot to, in my mind, to dream about.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "Why dreaming?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Well, when I was 18 years old, the big dream for me was to be Johnny Bench.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "When you were that 18-year-old Billy Ray, what was the big dream?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "I -- I like him, you know.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "So what do you feel about Justin?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "You know what, I think it was more met with Miley growing up under the circus tent of my life, realizing that, again, that's, you know, for -- in this business, the higher you go, the further you fall, knowing that in entertainment, you -- that's the -- there's a good side of it, that anything you can dream, you can be, have or do and it can go really, really high.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "When that happened, did you sit down with her and give her the life lesson about this is what's going to happen and these are the pitfalls?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Looking back at my life, some of the adversities I faced as a kid, to be honest, early on.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "What was the toughest moment when you look back?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "But where go you get that from?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "Thank you very much for saying that and it was an honor.", "docId": "130614pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Your parents or?", "qSentId": 631}]